My DMs have literally been crazy
for the past 2 weeks about how to do this process,
how to stop this, how to save this and my answer to most of y'all,
unless your situation is slightly unique,
is going to be the same with foreclosure,
with a custody battle, traffic court,
that has always been a problem
but for that foreclosure and custody battle,
them 2 is off the chain right now,
literally off the charts and my answer to you is gonna be to secure the account.
Every time it's not gonna change,
secure the account, stop using the name and stop going to court.
Don't go silent for the court though,
do not go silent. That's called acquiescence.
You have to allow them to know that you do not consent to come to court.
You are not making an appearance.
Tomorrow is the zoom. I tried to go live on here y'all,